/

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

**Effective & Last Updated On: 06-13-2024**

Alpha Media (“Alpha,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) is a diverse multimedia company sharing your favorite music, sports and news across a variety of platforms. In fulfilling this mission, we collect, use, and share certain information about you. We take your privacy seriously, and this Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand how and why we collect, use, and share your personal information. This Privacy Policy also describes certain choices and rights you may have.

This Privacy Policy covers Alpha’s privacy practices, including but not limited to all Alpha websites, including [www.alphamediausa.com](https://www.alphamediausa.com/) and the websites of our individual radio stations, and other online services (collectively, “Services”), as well as Alpha’s offline privacy practices.

This Privacy Policy, unless otherwise specified, applies to all U.S. consumers. Residents of California, Nevada and Virginia have additional privacy rights, and accordingly, some information in this Privacy Policy only applies if you are a resident of that state.

If you do not consent to the collection, use, or sharing of your information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with such information.

**Table of Contents**

**Section 1: General Privacy Practices**  

**Section 2: Notices and Rights for California Residents**  
[A. Consumer Rights Under California Law](#consumerrights)[B. How California Residents Can Exercise Their Rights](#carights)[C. How California Residents Can Designate an Authorized Agent](#authorizedagent)[D. How We Verify California Residents’ Requests to Know/Requests for Access and Requests for Deletion](#verifyresident)[E. Notice at Collection of Personal Information](#cacollection)[F. Notice of Right to Opt-Out of Sale of Personal Information](#caoptout)[G. Notice of Financial Incentive](#caincentive)

**Section 1: General Privacy Practices**

1. **Personal Information We Collect About You**

Alpha Media collects personal information—which is information that identifies you. We collect personal information from and about you. This section explains the categories of information we collect, as well as the sources from which we collect that information and the purposes for which we collect it.

**_Categories of Personal Information_****.** We may collect the following categories of personal information from you or about you when you engage with our Services:  
–  _Identifying information._ This includes name, e-mail address, telephone number, mobile phone number, geographic location, mailing address, date of birth, zip code, age and gender.  
– _Financial_ _Information._ When needed to process a transaction,  such as credit or debit card details.  
–  _Sensitive Information._ If you choose to share it with us, we may collect certain things such as age, race, and gender.  
– _Internet or other electronic network activity information._ This includes your IP address, unique device identifiers, and geolocation data. This could also include photos, videos, and other content that you allow access to from your device.  
–  _Analytics data._ This includes information about your interactions with our Services, including your interactions with songs, playlists, and/or audiovisual content; your interactions with other Alpha users; your interactions with advertising on our Services and information from the public profile of your social media account, including your connections and “likes.”  
–  _Communications._ This includes any communications you have with Alpha, including any user-generated content, such as photos, videos or similar content that you may share with us.  
–  _Usage information._ When you engage with our Services, we, as well as any third-party partners and/or service providers, may use a variety of technologies and services—including log files, device identifiers (like mobile advertising identifiers), location information, cookies, pixel tags, and analytics services—that automatically or passively collect information about how you accessed and used our Services. We or our third-party partners may also collect internet or other electronic network activity information, including browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with our Services.

**_Sources of Personal Information._** We may collect, the above-listed categories of personal information from the following sources:  
–  Directly from you through your interactions with our Services, including when you sign up for a text message or email subscription, access or download content, purchase items, or enter into contests or promotions.  
–  Automatically about you when you interact with our Services, including page clicks, time spent, or other automatically collected data.  
–  From cookies or other online tracking technologies, placed on our Services directly by Alpha or by our third-party partners.  
–  From social media platforms, like Twitter or Facebook.  
–  From joint marketing partners.  
–  From advertising network partners.  
–  From service providers, including analytics providers.  
–  From your friends and family, when they provide information about you to us.

**_Purposes for Collection._** We may use the above-listed categories of personal information for one or more of the following business purposes:  
–  To accomplish the purpose for which you provided the information. For example, if you provide your personal information to receive regular newsletters or text message updates.  
–  To process your requests, purchases, transactions, and payments and prevent transactional fraud.  
–  To administer our contests, promotions, and events, including by verifying location.  
–  To deliver content and product and service offerings relevant to your interests, including targeted and personalized offers and advertisements through our Services and third-party sites, and also via email or text message (pursuant to applicable law regarding consent).  
–  To measure, analyze, and report ad quality and effectiveness.  
–  To provide, support, personalize, and develop our Services.  
–  To link or combine your information with information we receive from others to help understand you and to provide you with better our Services and advertisements.  
–  To provide you with customer service support and to respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses.  
–  To communicate with you generally, including about your account and activities on our Services; or about changes to Alpha’s policies;  
–  To communicate with you, either directly or through one of our third-party partners, for marketing and promotional purposes via emails, newsletters, notifications, text messages, or other messages.  
–  To verify your identity.  
–  To help maintain the safety, security, and integrity of our Services.  
–  For testing, research, analysis, and product development, including to develop and improve our Services.  
–  For analytics and operations of our Services.  
–  To gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  
–  To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.  
–  To carry out obligations as an FCC-licensed broadcaster and other government or legal obligations.  
–  To carry out obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts we enter with you.  
–  For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.

**_Disclosures of Personal Information for a Business Purpose._** Alpha may disclose for a business purpose, the above-listed categories of personal information to the following categories of third-parties or service providers:  
–  Services providers, including data analytics providers, payment processors, and customer support services, among others;  
–  Advertising networks and advertising servers;  
–  Third-party marketing partners and sponsors;

– Analytics providers  
–  Sponsors and third-party partners for sweepstakes, contests, and promotions;  
–  Social networks;  
–  Alpha’s subsidiaries and affiliates;  
–  Entities that acquire us or all or substantially all of our assets, or assets related to our Services, or entities that engage in due diligence to consider doing so;  
–  Law enforcement

1. **Cookies and Online Tracking**

Our Services use a variety of online tracking devices or technologies, including log files, device identifiers (like mobile advertising identifiers), location information, cookies, pixel tags (also called web beacons or tracking beacons), and analytics services. We or our third-party partners or service providers may place cookies (which are small text files) on your device for a variety of reasons, including for security and to optimize your interaction on our Services. You may be able to opt-out of the use of certain cookies, although doing so may limit certain features on our Services. See [Your Choices below for more information on how to customize your cookie options.](https://www.alphamediausa.com/privacy-policy/#choices)

1. **Personalized Advertising**

We partner with various third parties to provide personalized content to you when you visit our Services. This may include advertising content from our partners. If you interact with certain advertising on our Services, the third-party partner may place a cookie on your device to collect information about you. These cookies may track your activities beyond our Services. We do not control the privacy practices of these third parties.

1. **Your Choices**

**_Cookies and Online Tracking_**. You can modify your cookie settings on your browser. If you delete or choose not to accept our cookies, certain features of our Services may not work as intended or be optimized or personalized.  
**_Online Behavioral Advertising._** You may opt-out of certain online behavioral advertising practices on our Services and on third-party sites and apps using the following programs and tools: (1) Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA), http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices/ and http://optout.aboutads.info, and/or (2) http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.  
**_Text Messages._** We will not send you text messages without your prior express consent as required by law. You may opt-out of receiving text messages from Alpha by texting STOP.  
**_Emails._** You can always unsubscribe from our commercial or promotional emails by clicking unsubscribe in those messages. We may still send you transactional and relational emails about your use of our Services.  
**_Do Not Track._** Our systems are not configured to recognize or respond to Do Not Track headers or signals.  
**_State-specific choices_**. Residents of certain states have additional choices, which are explained in Section 2-4 below.

1. **Security Safeguards**

Alpha uses reasonable and appropriate measures designed to protect your personal information. But we cannot guarantee the security of your information because no security measures are 100% effective.

1. **Amendments to Privacy Policy**

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy will be posted here. Please check this Privacy Policy frequently. If you do not agree or consent to these changes, do not continue to use our Services.

1. **Contact Information**

If you have any questions or concerns about the content in this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.987thebull.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

#### **Section 2: Privacy Notice for California Residents**

_This section only applies to California residents. The notices and rights in this section do not extend to individuals who are not California residents._

Privacy Notice for California residents is part of Alpha’s [Privacy Policy](https://www.alphamediausa.com/privacy-policy/) and includes details about the personal information we collect from California residents,  the purposes for which that personal information will be used, and the consumer rights that apply to California residents. For purposes of compliance with the CCPA, this Privacy Notice is also a Notice at Collection of Personal Information (“Notice at Collection”). We adopt this Privacy Notice in accordance with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020 (“CCPA”) and any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this Notice at Collection.

**_Personal Information We Collect About You._** Alpha collects personal information, which is information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked with a particular California consumer or household. In particular, we may collect the following categories of personal information from you or about you when you engage with our Services:

–  _Identifiers._ This includes name, e-mail address, telephone number, mobile phone number, geographic location, mailing address, date of birth, zip code, age and gender.  
_–_ _Financial_ _Information._ When needed to process a transaction, such as credit or debit card details.  
–  _Sensitive Information._ If you choose to share it with us, we may collect certain things such as age, race, and gender.  
– _Internet or other electronic network activity information._ This includes your IP address, unique device identifiers, and geolocation data. This could also include photos, videos, and other content that you allow access to from your device.  
–  _Analytics data._ This includes information about your interactions with our Services, including your interactions with songs, playlists, and/or audiovisual content; your interactions with other Alpha users; your interactions with advertising on our Services and information from the public profile of your social media account, including your connections and “likes.”  
–  _Communications._ This includes any communications you have with Alpha, including any user-generated content, such as photos, videos or similar content that you may share with us.  
–  _Usage information._ When you engage with our Services, we, as well as any third-party partners and/or service providers, may use a variety of technologies and services—including log files, device identifiers (like mobile advertising identifiers), location information, cookies, pixel tags, and analytics services—that automatically or passively collect information about how you accessed and used our Services. We or our third-party partners may also collect internet or other electronic network activity information, including browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with our Services.

**_How We Use Your Personal Information._** We may use each category of the personal information we collect for one or more of the following purposes:  
–  To accomplish the purpose for which you provided the information. For example, if you provide your personal information to receive regular newsletters or text message updates.  
–  To process your requests, purchases, transactions, and payments and prevent transactional fraud.  
–  To administer our contests, promotions, and events, including by verifying location.  
–  To deliver content and product and service offerings relevant to your interests, including targeted and personalized offers and advertisements through our Services and third-party sites, and also via email or text message (pursuant to applicable law regarding consent).  
–  To measure, analyze, and report ad quality and effectiveness.  
–  To provide, support, personalize, and develop our Services.  
–  To link or combine your information with information we receive from others to help understand you and to provide you with better our Services and advertisements.  
–  To provide you with customer service support and to respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses.  
–  To communicate with you generally, including about your account and activities on our Services; or about changes to Alpha’s policies;  
–  To communicate with you, either directly or through one of our third-party partners, for marketing and promotional purposes via emails, newsletters, notifications, text messages, or other messages.  
–  To verify your identity.  
–  To help maintain the safety, security, and integrity of our Services.  
–  For testing, research, analysis, and product development, including to develop and improve our Services.  
–  For analytics and operations of our Services.  
–  To gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  
–  To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.  
–  To carry out obligations as an FCC-licensed broadcaster and other government or legal obligations.  
–  To carry out obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts we enter with you.  
–  For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.  
–  We may also sell your information for one of above-listed purposes, see [Sale of Personal Information.](https://www.alphamediausa.com/privacy-policy/#sale)

1. **Consumer Rights Under California Law**

**_Right to Know._**  California residents have the right to request that Alpha disclose what information we have collected, used, disclosed, or sold about you. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request for such information, we may disclose to you, based on your specific request:  
–  The categories of personal information we collected about you;  
–  The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected;  
–  The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information;  
–  The categories of third-parties with whom we shared your personal information;  
–  If we disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, the personal information categories that each category of recipients obtained;  
–  If we sold your personal information for a business purpose, the personal information categories that each category of recipients purchased; or  
–  Specific pieces of data

**_Right to Request Deletion_**. California residents have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we have collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. 

**_Right to Correct_**_._ California residents have the right to ask that we correct inaccurate information that we have about you.

**_Right to Limit the Use of Sensitive Personal Information._** In certain circumstances, California residents have the right to ask that we limit the collection and use of sensitive personal information.

**_Right to Opt-Out of Sale or Sharing of Personal Information._**  California residents have the right to direct businesses that sell personal information to not sell your personal information (the “right to opt-out”).

We use digital technologies, including online identifiers, to provide you with personalized marketing and perform online analytics.  We may disclose these online identifiers to our analytics and marketing partners. The CCPA considers this to be Selling and Sharing of your personal information. Alpha does not have actual knowledge that it Sells or Shares Personal Information about consumers under 16 years of age.   

Additionally, we may share your information with co-sponsors of our contests and promotions, which also could be considered a Sale under the CCPA.

You have the right to opt-out of Selling and Sharing. For more information about these activities and to exercise your right to opt-out of Selling and Sharing, please see our [“Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information”](https://www.987thebull.com/notice-of-right-to-opt-out) page, which contains our Notice of the Right to Opt-Out and opt-out mechanism.     

**_Right to Opt-In to Sales of Personal Information for Minors Under 16._** We do not sell the personal information of California residents we actually know are less than 16 years of age, unless we receive affirmative authorization (the “right to opt-in”) from either the consumer who is 13-15 years of age, or the parent or guardian of a consumer less than 13 years of age. Consumers who opt-in to personal information sales may opt-out of future sales at any time.

**_Right to Non-Discrimination_**. California residents have the right not to be discriminated against for having exercised the rights established by the CCPA. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights.

We may, however, offer you certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt in consent, which you may revoke at any time. For more information about the CCPA-permitted financial incentives that we offer, see [Notice of Financial Incentive.](#caincentive)

**_California Shine the Light Rights._** Under California’s Shine the Light law, California residents may request certain details about how their information is shared with third-parties for direct marketing purposes.

1. **How California Residents Can Exercise Their Rights**

You or your authorized agent may submit a verifiable consumer request using the contact information listed below.

The verifiable consumer request must do the following:  
–  Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative.  
–  Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

To exercise any of the rights listed above, please:  
Call us at 866-593-4937;  
Fill out this [form](https://www.alphamediausa.com/ccpa-opt-out/); or  
Email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.987thebull.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

1. **How We Verify California Residents’ Requests to Know/Requests for Access and Requests for Deletion**

We will not respond to certain consumer requests unless we can verify your identity to a reasonable degree of certainty. To verify your identity, when feasible, we will use information about you that we already have; however, we may need to request additional information, which we will use only for the purposes of verification. We may also use a third-party identity verification service.

The information we need to verify your request will depend on the nature and scope of your request. Upon receipt of your request, we will notify you if we need additional information from you to verify your request.

1. **Notice of Financial Incentive**

This Notice of Financial Incentive is part of Alpha’s [Privacy Policy](https://www.alphamediausa.com/privacy-policy/) and includes an explanation of financial incentives we offer California residents. This Notice of Financial Incentive applies solely to California residents (“California consumers” or “you”). We adopt this Notice of Financial Incentive in accordance with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) and any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this Notice of Financial Incentive.

**_Summary of Financial Incentive Offered._** Alpha conducts contests and promotions. Listeners who share certain personal information with us—for example, their name and contact information, such as an email address or social media account details—have a chance of to win the contest or promotion. Alpha also offers listeners the opportunity to sign up to receive early access information for certain shows, or participate in similar promotions, by providing personal information such as their name and an email address. Each individual contest, promotion, or early ticket offer is governed by its own terms, and the exact financial incentive offered will be detailed there. Alpha values the data of listeners that participate in our incentives because it allows us to engage with and reward our loyal listeners with promotions and other incentives tailored to their interests and level of engagement with us.  The value of each consumer’s data depends on the listener’s level of engagement with us and our sponsors compared to the level of engagement of listeners that do not participate in our incentives.

**_Opt-in to Financial Incentive Program._** For participation in incentive programs related to our contests and promotions, you must provide your opt-in consent. To opt-in to Alpha’s financial incentive for an individual contest or promotion, go to [alphamediausa.com](https://www.alphamediausa.com/). You may revoke your consent at any time by doing one of the following:

Call us at 866-593-4937;  
Fill out this [form](https://www.alphamediausa.com/ccpa-opt-out/); or  
Email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.987thebull.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Section 3: Additional Information for Nevada Residents**

This section of the Privacy Policy only applies to residents of Nevada. If you are not a resident of Nevada, this section does not apply to you. Terms that are capitalized are defined in the Nevada law.

As defined under Nevada law, we do not sell Covered Information.  However, Nevada Consumers may submit a verified request at any time directing that we not make any Sale of any Covered Information that we have collected or will collect about the consumer, as defined under the Nevada law. To submit such a request, you can email [\[email protected\]](https://www.987thebull.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Section 4: Additional Information for Virginia Residents**

This section of the Privacy Policy only applies to residents of Virginia. If you are not a resident of Virginia, this section does not apply to you. Terms that are capitalized are defined in the Virginia law.

Pursuant Virginia’s Consumer Data Protection Act, as amended (“VCDPA”), Virginia residents may have certain data privacy rights. This section describes your rights under the VCDPA and supplements our privacy policy. 

Your Virginia Rights: If you are a resident of Virginia, you have the following consumer rights:  

**Right of Access.** Virginia residents may confirm whether or not we are processing your personal information and access such personal information; 

**Right of Correction**. Virginia residents have the right to correct personal data that is inaccurate; 

**Right of Deletion.** Virginia residents have the right to delete your personal information; 

**Right of Portability**. Virginia residents have the right to obtain a copy of your personal information that you have previously provided to us; and 

**Right to Opt-Out.**  Virginia residents have the right to opt-out of targeted advertising, the sale of personal information, or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you

Targeted Advertising:  We use digital technologies, including online identifiers, to provide you with personalized advertisements.  We may disclose these online identifiers to our advertising partners. The VCDPA considers this to be a Targeted Advertising and Virginia residents have the right to opt-out of this processing [here](https://www.987thebull.com/notice-of-right-to-opt-out).

Additionally, we may share your information with co-sponsors of our contests and promotions, which also could be considered a Sale under the VCDPA.  To opt-out of this sharing of your information or to exercise your other rights, please contact us using one of the methods listed below. 

Call us at 866-593-4937;  
Fill out this [form](https://www.alphamediausa.com/ccpa-opt-out/); or  
Email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.987thebull.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

We will not respond to certain consumer requests unless we can verify your identity to a reasonable degree of certainty. To verify your identity, when feasible, we will use information about you that we already have; however, we may need to request additional information, which we will use only for the purposes of verification. We may also use a third-party identity verification service.

The information we need to verify your request will depend on the nature and scope of your request. Upon receipt of your request, we will notify you if we need additional information from you to verify your request.

If we cannot verify your identity, we may deny your request in whole or in part. Under the VCDPA, you may appeal our decision with regard to your request. To do so, please send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.987thebull.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), with the word “Appeal” in the subject line. 

SMS PRIVACY POLICY
==================

Most Recent Update: 06-13-2024

This Privacy Policy explains how Alpha Media LLC collects, uses and discloses personal information of its subscribers, prospective subscribers, or former subscribers to its SMS programs. We have adopted the following policies and procedures to safeguard the personal information about you in our possession.

### Our Privacy Policy for Consumers That Opt-in to SMS Messages

* Through the use of our SMS programs, we may collect personally identifiable information such as mobile numbers, names, locations, and any other personal information you may choose to provide to us.
* Personally identifiable information may be used internally by Alpha Media LLC for the sole purpose of executing our SMS programs and will not be shared with any third party affiliates for any reason. Our treatment of all personally identifiable information is consistent with this privacy policy.
* We do not sell or rent customer information obtained through SMS origination.
* Our policy is to require all employees and companies providing services on our behalf to keep customer information confidential.
* Our SMS privacy policy applies to potential subscribers as well as current and former subscribers.
* You will only receive messages applicable to the campaign that you have opted-in for unless you have provided us with express consent to receive additional forms of communication from Alpha Media LLC
* If you wish to be removed from receiving future communications, you can opt out by texting STOP.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page and/or communicated to you in other ways if required by law. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or consent to these updates or changes, do not continue to use the Platform.

Recently Played
---------------

|     |
| --- |
| If I Didn&Apos;T Love YouJason Aldean & Carrie Underwood<br><br>5:35pm |
| ChevroletDustin Lynch Ft Jelly Roll<br><br>5:32pm |
| She&Apos;S Somebody'S DaughterDrew Baldridge<br><br>5:29pm |
| The Kind Of Love We MakeLuke Combs<br><br>5:25pm |
| Thinkin &Apos;Bout MeMorgan Wallen<br><br>5:23pm |

* * *

You Might Also Like
-------------------

[Country News](https://www.987thebull.com/category/country/)[### Jordan Davis is "all gas, no brakes" and TR's "feeling very jacked" as CMA Fest 2024 gets underway](https://www.987thebull.com/jordan-davis-is-all-gas-no-brakes-and-trs-feeling-very-jacked-as-cma-fest-2024-gets-underway/)

* * *

* * *

[Country News](https://www.987thebull.com/category/country/)[### Luke Bryan on his first time playing CMA Fest: "I remember just being as nervous as you could be"](https://www.987thebull.com/luke-bryan-on-his-first-time-playing-cma-fest-i-remember-just-being-as-nervous-as-you-could-be/)

* * *

    If you have a disability preventing you from viewing this file, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.987thebull.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
    
* [CA Residents: Privacy Notice at Collection of Personal Information](https://www.987thebull.com/privacy-policy#caresidents)
* [CA/VA Residents: Do Not Sell Or Share My Personal Information](https://www.987thebull.com/notice-of-right-to-opt-out)

Discover Brands By...
---------------------

Market

Format

State

* Alaska
* California
* Illinois
* Iowa
* Kansas
* Kentucky
* Louisiana
* Michigan
* Minnesota
* Mississippi
* Missouri
* Nebraska
* Ohio
* Oregon
* Pennsylvania
* South Carolina
* South Dakota
* Texas
* Utah
* Virginia
* Washington
* Wisconsin

Featured Brands
---------------

Sports • Midwest

Top 40 • Eastern

Country • Western

Spanish • Western

98.7 The Bull is a part of Alpha Media LLC.  
© 2024 Alpha Media LLC. All Rights Reserved.

Our Brands
